[
  {
    "front": "Hello",
    "back": "Hallo"
  },
  {
    "front": "Yes",
    "back": "Ja"
  },
  {
    "front": "No",
    "back": "Nein"
  },
  {
    "front": "Time",
    "back": "Zeit"
  },
  {
    "front": "deeply relaxed",
    "back": "Tiefenentspannt"
  },
  {
    "front": "itself/herself",
    "back": "Sich"
  },
  {
    "front": "her",
    "back": "Ihrem/ihren"
  },
  {
    "front": "grant/take",
    "back": "Gegönnt"
  },
  {
    "front": "time out/break",
    "back": "Die Auszeit"
  },
  {
    "front": "the weeks",
    "back": "Die Wochen"
  },
  {
    "front": "last",
    "back": "Letzten"
  },
  {
    "front": "were",
    "back": "Waren"
  },
  {
    "front": "stressful",
    "back": "Stressig"
  },
  {
    "front": "went",
    "back": "Gefahren"
  },
  {
    "front": "at",
    "back": "An"
  },
  {
    "front": "North Sea",
    "back": "Die Nordsee"
  },
  {
    "front": "once",
    "back": "Einmal"
  },
  {
    "front": "sometimes",
    "back": "Manchmal"
  },
  {
    "front": "work",
    "back": "Die Arbeit"
  },
  {
    "front": "thought",
    "back": "Gedacht"
  },
  {
    "front": "again",
    "back": "Wieder"
  },
  {
    "front": "return/back",
    "back": "Zurück"
  },
  {
    "front": "into the",
    "back": "Ins"
  },
  {
    "front": "office",
    "back": "Das Büro"
  },
  {
    "front": "mood",
    "back": "Gelaunt"
  },
  {
    "front": "welcomed",
    "back": "Begrüst"
  },
  {
    "front": "eating",
    "back": "Isst"
  },
  {
    "front": "pancake",
    "back": "Der Pfannkuchen"
  },
  {
    "front": "that",
    "back": "Dass"
  },
  {
    "front": "are",
    "back": "Gibt"
  },
  {
    "front": "do",
    "back": "Tun"
  },
  {
    "front": "should",
    "back": "Soll"
  },
  {
    "front": "where",
    "back": "Wo"
  },
  {
    "front": "begin",
    "back": "Anfangen"
  },
  {
    "front": "quickly/fast",
    "back": "Schnell"
  },
  {
    "front": "still",
    "back": "Noch"
  },
  {
    "front": "mouth",
    "back": "Der Mund"
  },
  {
    "front": "further",
    "back": "Weiteren"
  },
  {
    "front": "wipes",
    "back": "Wischt"
  },
  {
    "front": "his",
    "back": "Seine"
  },
  {
    "front": "sticky",
    "back": "Klebrigen"
  },
  {
    "front": "am happy",
    "back": "Freue"
  },
  {
    "front": "happy",
    "back": "Glücklich"
  },
  {
    "front": "to see again",
    "back": "Wiederzusehen"
  },
  {
    "front": "then",
    "back": "Dann"
  },
  {
    "front": "want",
    "back": "Wollen/möchte"
  },
  {
    "front": "both",
    "back": "Beide"
  },
  {
    "front": "to see",
    "back": "Sehen"
  },
  {
    "front": "was",
    "back": "War"
  },
  {
    "front": "were",
    "back": "Warren"
  },
  {
    "front": "forward",
    "back": "Vorwärts"
  },
  {
    "front": "backward",
    "back": "Rückwärts"
  },
  {
    "front": "back",
    "back": "Der Rücken"
  },
  {
    "front": "in+das",
    "back": "Ins"
  },
  {
    "front": "book",
    "back": "Das Buch"
  },
  {
    "front": "table",
    "back": "Der Tisch"
  },
  {
    "front": "chair",
    "back": "Der Stuhl"
  },
  {
    "front": "house",
    "back": "Das Haus"
  },
  {
    "front": "car",
    "back": "Das Auto"
  },
  {
    "front": "dog",
    "back": "Der Hund"
  },
  {
    "front": "cat",
    "back": "Die Katze"
  },
  {
    "front": "water",
    "back": "Das Wasser"
  },
  {
    "front": "food",
    "back": "Das Essen"
  },
  {
    "front": "city",
    "back": "Die Stadt"
  },
  {
    "front": "Pronunciation",
    "back": "Die Aussprache (f)"
  },
  {
    "front": "the superhero",
    "back": "der Superheld"
  },
  {
    "front": "the teacher",
    "back": "der Lehrer"
  },
  {
    "front": "the holiday/vacation",
    "back": "der Urlaub"
  },
  {
    "front": "the car",
    "back": "der Wagen"
  },
  {
    "front": "the forest",
    "back": "der Wald"
  },
  {
    "front": "the peace",
    "back": "der Frieden"
  },
  {
    "front": "the sky",
    "back": "der Himmel"
  },
  {
    "front": "the wind",
    "back": "der Wind"
  },
  {
    "front": "the rain",
    "back": "der Regen"
  },
  {
    "front": "the suit",
    "back": "der Anzug"
  },
  {
    "front": "the beard",
    "back": "der Bart"
  },
  {
    "front": "the backpack",
    "back": "der Rucksack"
  },
  {
    "front": "the umbrella",
    "back": "der Schirm"
  },
  {
    "front": "the fish",
    "back": "der Fisch"
  },
  {
    "front": "the chair",
    "back": "der Stuhl"
  },
  {
    "front": "the coffee",
    "back": "der Kaffee"
  },
  {
    "front": "the mug",
    "back": "der Becher"
  },
  {
    "front": "the cake",
    "back": "der Kuchen"
  },
  {
    "front": "the plate",
    "back": "der Teller"
  },
  {
    "front": "the thought",
    "back": "der Gedanke"
  },
  {
    "front": "the plan",
    "back": "der Plan"
  },
  {
    "front": "the moon",
    "back": "der Mond"
  },
  {
    "front": "the courage",
    "back": "der Mut"
  },
  {
    "front": "the song",
    "back": "der Gesang"
  },
  {
    "front": "the bird",
    "back": "der Vogel"
  },
  {
    "front": "the queen",
    "back": "die Königin"
  },
  {
    "front": "the castle",
    "back": "die Burg"
  },
  {
    "front": "the idea",
    "back": "die Idee"
  },
  {
    "front": "the jacket",
    "back": "die Jacke"
  },
  {
    "front": "the blouse",
    "back": "die Bluse"
  },
  {
    "front": "the post office",
    "back": "die Post"
  },
  {
    "front": "the queue",
    "back": "die Schlange"
  },
  {
    "front": "the time",
    "back": "die Zeit"
  },
  {
    "front": "the newspaper",
    "back": "die Zeitung"
  },
  {
    "front": "the clock",
    "back": "die Uhr"
  },
  {
    "front": "the sausage",
    "back": "die Wurst"
  },
  {
    "front": "the region",
    "back": "die Region"
  },
  {
    "front": "the credit card",
    "back": "die Kreditkarte"
  },
  {
    "front": "the bag",
    "back": "die Tasche"
  },
  {
    "front": "the door",
    "back": "die Tür"
  },
  {
    "front": "the garage",
    "back": "die Garage"
  },
  {
    "front": "the limousine",
    "back": "die Limousine"
  },
  {
    "front": "the banana",
    "back": "die Banane"
  },
  {
    "front": "the engine",
    "back": "die Maschine"
  },
  {
    "front": "the city",
    "back": "die Stadt"
  },
  {
    "front": "the night",
    "back": "die Nacht"
  },
  {
    "front": "the disco",
    "back": "die Disco"
  },
  {
    "front": "the music",
    "back": "die Musik"
  },
  {
    "front": "the freedom",
    "back": "die Freiheit"
  },
  {
    "front": "the wall",
    "back": "die Wand"
  },
  {
    "front": "the princess",
    "back": "die Prinzessin"
  },
  {
    "front": "the piece of news",
    "back": "die Neuigkeit"
  },
  {
    "front": "the baby",
    "back": "das Baby"
  },
  {
    "front": "the bed",
    "back": "das Bett"
  },
  {
    "front": "the glass",
    "back": "das Glas"
  },
  {
    "front": "the window",
    "back": "das Fenster"
  },
  {
    "front": "the toy",
    "back": "das Spielzeug"
  },
  {
    "front": "the car",
    "back": "das Auto"
  },
  {
    "front": "the picture",
    "back": "das Bild"
  },
  {
    "front": "the lunch",
    "back": "das Mittagessen"
  },
  {
    "front": "the vegetables",
    "back": "das Gemüse"
  },
  {
    "front": "the water",
    "back": "das Wasser"
  },
  {
    "front": "the beer",
    "back": "das Bier"
  },
  {
    "front": "the video",
    "back": "das Video"
  },
  {
    "front": "the mobile phone",
    "back": "das Handy"
  },
  {
    "front": "the song",
    "back": "das Lied"
  },
  {
    "front": "the horse",
    "back": "das Pferd"
  },
  {
    "front": "the face",
    "back": "das Gesicht"
  },
  {
    "front": "the light",
    "back": "das Licht"
  },
  {
    "front": "the secret",
    "back": "das Geheimnis"
  },
  {
    "front": "the paradise",
    "back": "das Paradies"
  },
  {
    "front": "the pleasure",
    "back": "das Vergnügen"
  },
  {
    "front": "the towel",
    "back": "das Handtuch"
  },
  {
    "front": "the book",
    "back": "das Buch"
  },
  {
    "front": "outer space",
    "back": "das All"
  }
]